hamidashita kaze wo atsumete mitai na
I want to try and gather the unrestrained winds
nami no saki tsutatte kanata e kaketeku
I'll run toward the horizon alongside the wave crests
kakugo wa kimatteru
I've made my decision
michi wa tookutemo
even if there's a long way to go on that road
egaita mirai e tsudzuiteru
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
toki ga bokura wo sekashite kodou ga supiido agetetta
time rushes us, the heartbeat speeds up
yume no naka de mezametemo onaji hikari wo sagashita
when I woke in the middle of a dream, I kept searching for that same light
kagayaku hoshizora no shita kazoekirenai seiza to kage
under the shining star-lit sky, with countless constellations and shadows
sono saki ni kimi wa nani wo nani wo mitsumete iru darou
there was something beyond that, what were you gazing at?
nani wo mitsumete iru darou
what were you gazing at?
Hasn't this increased
since last month?
Yes, it has.
It's now widely known
in distant lands
that you were appointed to Hokage,
Tsunade-sama.
Bills have started to come in addressed
to the Village Hidden in Leaves.
Hokage is not something to take on.
My name is Tsunade...
I'm the Fifth Hokage
of the Village Hidden in Leaves.
My concern now is a debt
that absolutely will not go down...
And...
Grandma Tsunade!
— Hey, wait!
— Naruto!
— Lemme go!
— Calm down!
If there aren't any missions,
let me go search for Sasuke!
You've been told to train,
haven't you, Naruto?!
Grandma Tsunade!
That...
Dig here, arf-arf!
Search for the
Buried Treasure
I won't let you through!
Goal!
Too bad.
But it's totally obvious since
it's the same person doing it.
There haven't been
any missions lately, either.
I wonder if the Pervy Sage will
come back soon...
I can't train by myself...
What, there was someone here
before me?
Kiba... Akamaru...
Here I thought I could take
my time to train.
Are you by yourself?
Where are Hinata and Shino?
Shino is backing up another team
with Kurenai-sensei...
Hinata said she'd train at home.
Is it like we've lost our jobs?
Don't say that...
I'll feel empty-hearted...
Naruto! Kiba!
Hinata...
Weren't you training at home?
There was a call from the Hokage.
She wants us to come immediately.
Then...
All right! Our first mission in a while!
Treasure hunting?
That's right. This person here,
an old acquaintance of mine,
is our client this time around...
My name is Kaisen Agari.
Please look at this.
This is a map indicating
the location of the treasure.
It seems a treasure worth several
hundred million ryo lies buried there.
Several hundred million?!
If I were to eat Ichiraku's
special portion ramen everyday...
I don't think you could eat all that even
if you spent your whole life eating...
Awesome!
But it's on the map, right?
Is this a job to go to the trouble
of asking Shinobi to do?
Yes. The treasure is in a location
difficult for ordinary people to get to.
Even I tried getting there...
but there was no way.
So it's the Shinobi's turn, huh?
The deadline is in three days.
If you succeed, there will be
a special reward from Agari.
Proceed with caution!
— Yes!
A mission like this is a cinch!
Indeed, it isn't a difficult mission.
However... if you fail...!
— What?!
Hey, wait!
If you fail...
you will go back to the Academy!
— What?!
You'll re-enroll in the Academy
and re-do your Ninja training
from square one.
Why us...?
I looked up your mission success rate
over these past few months...
Naruto! You're decisively poor!
What?!
In particular, the success rate
when you team up
with Inuzuka Kiba and Hyuga Hinata
is hopelessly low!
Now that she mentions it,
it's the members we failed
an earlier mission with...
We also failed before when
four of us, including Shino,
went looking for Bikochu Beetles...
Something sounds familiar, right?
But, just Naruto aside,
why should we also have
to go back to the Academy?
Collective responsibility is fundamental
in Ninja teams.
Everyone takes responsibility
for a failure.
Got it?!
It... it'll be okay. No way should we fail
at hunting for treasure...
If you don't drag us down.
What?! Don't you be dragging us down!
If we fail... we'll have to study
with these kids, right...?
Hey, what's up?
Naruto, Kiba, Hinata,
all three of you together?
Iruka-sensei...
You guys must have come
to miss the Academy, huh?
You could come back if you like.
I'll never go back!
What's with them...?
I'll make this mission a success
no matter what
and put Grandma Tsunade
to shame!
And I'll have no part of
going back...
to the Academy on account
of associating with you.
The failures until now
are a collective responsibility.
It's not just my responsibility!
I don't know about that.
The success rate of our team
without you in it is high.
Then I'll prove on this mission
who it is who really drags us down!
That's just what I want.
I wonder if this will be okay?
It's a dead-end!
So this is as far as
there's a path, huh...?
There's a river up ahead.
How should we cross it...?
Then, here, here.
We should cut straight through, right?!
Are you an idiot?
Mountain terrain isn't that simple.
I would go... this way.
Are you an idiot?
That's totally the long way around.
Then you want to compete
to see which is faster?
No way will I lose!
All right! The finish line
is that boulder!
Start! Let's go, Akamaru!
This will be a cinch!
What? What?
Wait, Naruto!
Naruto...
What?
It seems we're climbing up
quite a bit...
It's okay!
Naruto!
It's... okay.
We should be totally faster
than Kiba, so...!
Yes! I win!
Something smells good...
So you finally made it, huh?
Kiba!
You were so late I went ahead
and got some food ready...
Now then... which way?
We should...
we should just cut right though this!
Naruto!
Good grief...
Water...
Here, water.
This way's definitely faster!
I sure slept well.
Akamaru and I often
train in mountains like this...
We know a lot more about
the mountains than you guys.
Shut up!
Shut up, I say!
Don't be acting all big just because
you won two or three times!
Not two or three times.
Five times!
Stop it! Naruto! Kiba!
Naruto and the others
should be there pretty soon, huh...?
This mission looks easy at a glance.
But it won't go that easily...
They'll probably realize that.
A limestone cave, huh...?
But...
Jeez, hurry up already!
You said the buried treasure is
in a limestone cave, right?
Just a minute!
The limestone cave is supposed
to be further ahead.
We shouldn't have been able
to find it this easily...
It's not like there are
that many limestone caves!
So here's fine...
Let's go, Hinata.
Right...
Hey, wait, you two!
I can't see anything...
Oh, it's a dead-end...
It can't be!
Naruto! Hinata!
Look out! Run, you two!
Wha...?
This... couldn't be over...
That person said it'd be okay
at just this extent...
What happened...?
By any chance,
was an enemy after us?
No... Akamaru's saying
he didn't smell anyone.
It was probably an accident...
I told you this wasn't the right place!
But, as a person,
if you're looking for a limestone cave
and there's one right in front of you,
one would usually think
that's the place, right?!
Don't be getting smart with me.
Here I saved your butt!
I didn't ask you to save me.
What?!
Hey... you two...
A shard from the ceiling
hit you, huh...?
You okay?
It seems I'm the one
dragging us down...
Not at all!
If I had been more cautious...
At the end of the day,
it's your fault, Naruto.
Kiba!
Nevertheless, I'll have no part of
going back to the Academy
on account of associating
with you, Naruto...
Akamaru and I will find the treasure.
What're you saying, Kiba?!
There's no point if
we don't all do it together!
I'm... okay, so...
From here on, there will be locations
along the way so rough
they are beyond comparison
to those up until this point...
It'll be nothing but places that
really only a Shinobi can get through!
It'd be absolutely impossible
for someone with an injured leg.
Besides... we can't just leave someone
who's injured, right?
We need someone to stay with her.
Then it doesn't have to be me...
Can you find the treasure by yourself?
You can't read a map worth a damn
and you don't know the mountains...
To be straight...
we've wasted a ton of time
on your account, so!
Rest easy.
After I find the treasure,
you won't have to go back
to the Academy...
Let's go, Akamaru!
Hey! Wait, Kiba!
Damn it...!
Now.
Naruto!
Are you awake, Naruto?
Hinata...
Naruto!
There are... two Hinatas!
Naruto...
Hinata, did you use a Clone Jutsu?
Could it be... you were twins?!
— No!
Then...
One of you transformed into Hinata
with a Transformation Jutsu, huh...?
I can't... tell you apart at all...
I'm the real one!
Your voices are also
exactly the same!
I know.
At a time like this,
I should ask a question
that only the real one knows.
I'll come right out and ask!
What's Hinata's father's name?
— Hiashi Hyuga.
Oh, yeah. As for me,
I didn't know Hinata's father's name.
What?!
— Naruto...
At a time like this,
if Kiba and Akamaru were here...
Here they could tell by smell
which one is the real one...
Nope. It'd be impossible even
for a Ninja Hound...
What?
This isn't just an ordinary
Transformation Jutsu, so...
Mister... As I recall,
you're the client this time around...
What are you doing here?
It wasn't buried treasure that I wanted...
It was your faces.
Faces...?
I already got... your face...
I'm Uzumaki Naruto!
That's... me...
I guess I'll be setting out
to get the last face...
Leave it to me!
This is the place...
This inside of the cave
is as the map says...
There's no doubt.
It's under this rock, huh?
I'll go in one shot!
This, huh...?
I found it surprisingly easy.
What is it, Akamaru?
Kiba? That's you there, isn't it, Kiba?
Kiba...?
Naruto... Hinata...
I told you guys to go
on back first, didn't I?!
Come on! Come on! Here we went
to the trouble of coming!
This mission is for the three of us, so...
Hinata... is your injury okay?
Yeah... I became able to move
after resting a bit, so...
You already found the treasure?!
Then let's take it back
to the village quick!
Right...
Wait... How did they get here
so fast without a map?
And moreover,
Naruto has zero sense of direction...
And Hinata has an injured leg...
Akamaru... doesn't seem to be feeling
any particular suspicion.
Am I being paranoid...?
It seems they're back.
Kiba! Akamaru!
Heh! Didn't we tell you?
Even a Ninja Hound's nose
can't tell the difference...
Let's begin.
Face Copying Jutsu!
What's that...?
We also copied faces like this.
As you can see,
when performing
the Face Copying Jutsu,
the person being copied
must be close by.
And moreover,
it takes a degree of time.
But once a face has been copied once,
it's an impeccable Transformation Jutsu
that is beyond even
a family's recognition.
No way...
Kiba! Wake up! Kiba!
What the hell are you...?!
I'm Inuzuka Kiba.
You guys...
What's the big idea?!
— Kiba!
Those are the real ones, huh...?
Who the hell are you guys?
The name of our clan
is the Kedouin Clan.
We're a clan that possesses
the secret Face Copying Jutsu.
Why our faces?
We're going to return to the
Village Hidden in Leaves in your place,
and mess up the village good!
kaze ga fuite aa
the wind blows
itai kienai omoi
the pain, the memories won't disappear
nani wo motte ikou ka
what should be brought along?
atsumete hitotsu
assemble them into a piece
nido to nai nido to nai
there is no second chance, never
suteru nante baka mitai
how foolish it is to throw away
mujaki ni natte aa
acting so innocently
imeeji
the images
kitto sore wa owaranai
it probably will not end
ai no mune kogase
burn that love-filled heart
sen no yume watare
sail across a thousand dreams
juuoumujin kakete
running freely
te ni tsukamu sekai
to take hold of the world in hand
kumo ga chigirete
the clouds scatter
hi ga mata ochite
the sun sets yet again
hitori no pareedo ga ugokidasu
the solo parade begins to move
bouken kichijitsu shinpaku joushou
adventure, lucky day, geart beat, rising
meian souguu seimei souai
decisive, encounter, life, mutual love
Like I said,
nothing good ever comes from
a mission together with you, Naruto.
This isn't the time to be complaining.
They're intending to
head for the village.
Then, how do we get out of here?
— Listen.
— With Rasengan, I'II...
No good. They'll notice.
— I can...
— Then use your Fang-Over-Fang.
— It'd be the same, you idiot.
— That's why I said...
— Then, what do we do?
— Use that, I'm telling you...
Naruto!
— Don't stop me, Hinata.
Not that, I mean I'll...
—- Oh, that.
— Oh, that.
Next time:
"Dash, Wonder, Zigzag Run! Chased, Chased and Mistaken.!"